	Deepa Rani
 Student no- 300365050                                 Introduction 

The video discusses the role of Management Information Systems (MIS) in business intelligence and analytics, including data visualization, data mining, predictive analysis, and reporting. The video explains the purpose of Management Information Systems (MIS) in the business industry and the tools used to edit the video. Essentially, Management Information Systems (MIS) assist business companies in producing reports to influence their direction positively. Its purpose is to set performance goals. The system ensures that the proper data is collected from all the different sources, processed, filtered, and sent to all necessary areas. The framework is expected to satisfy the data needs of an individual, a gathering of people, and the administration functionaries: the upper management and managers. This report provides an overview of how Management Information System (MIS) is implemented, explains the video-making process, the analysis of the video-making process and the results, and the conclusion. 

 
                      

 

                        